I'm a very environmental person.
For example I've stopped burning oil to heat up my apartment.
Now I only do it for fun.
Eco is an environmental game where you build stuff so you can destroy the environment.
Probably notice the similarities to another mine-crafting game, but that's the point.
They have recycled
Today I'm going to show you how to create a perfect, sustainable world.
You play the game with hundreds of people.
You craft the planet,
build an economy,
establish laws,
Together, you form a civilization.
Gonna play it alone.
Yeah... [Intro]
Nature is nice.
Probably because it's a video game so no mosquitoes.
I should do the tutorial...
...wait, "The Meteor"?
Countdown until meteor impact. You're supposed to stop a space rock.
What kind of environmental message is that?
It doesn't matter what you do because
The Universe Will Whoop Your Ass.
Whatever, 30 real-time days. If I had that time in Minecraft I could build the Vatican. Let's get to work!
To make a perfect world, we need to find food, build shelter and not drill for oil.
Let's start with the first one, I'm staaarving.
Hmm, can't eat that bison..
Because of the environment I'm doing an ecological vegan diet.
Only in the game of course.
In real life I have taste buds.
There's nothing more vegan than tomatoes.
They grow everywhere and come with variety!
For breakfast, a raw tomato. Tomato soup for lunch and for dinner -
You can eat ketchup.
So to save the planet, we will eat wild tomatoes
Now, for shelter. Time to build a house, the best investment since the Bronze Age.
Chop wood, chop wood.. This is -
Very boring.
Really regretting playing this multiplayer game alone.
I guess I'm not alone, I have these bisons..
Get out of here yankee cow! If I can't eat you, you serve no purpose!
Did it!
That took 15 days..
What the- why's there a nicer house here!
Did YOU build this?
That's unfair, there's two of you!
Also you don't need houses! You're bisons!
Gonna propose a law which makes it ILLEGAL for bisons to build stuff.
The house is missing a door. To get that we need a carpentry table.
That requires 20 more logs.
This is... not getting any more fun...
And there are way more bisons now.
I'm noticing the tomato farm!
We are supposed to eat wild tomatoes , don't force me to ban bison farming too.
We did it!
And now for a door, we need MORE LOGS
Easy, peasy...
Hey, what are you guys doing now?
Creating a bloomery?
That's terrible for the environment, shame on you!
I'm confiscating this.
Now that I have a door and this.
I can melt iron ore... But to find iron I have to travel quite far...
If any of you buffaloes break the law while I'm gone there WILL be angry letters.
Bet that scared them, time to destroy rocks.
This is not as boring as cutting logs!
Still very boring. With this iron I can get some great tools that will really speed up my progress-
Wait, asphalt?
Oh, come on!
I was gone for one hour and bisons have established a bison country!
With bison schools
Bison shops
And bison
Starbuckses™
This can't get any worse.. IS THAT AN EXCAVATOR?
I just invented the chair!
-ohh no. If you have digging machines does that mean you have-
AWWWWWW!
You did the one thing we promised we weren't gonna do!
Bisons, you are just... the WORST animal!
What happened to my house?
You've furnished it. In a way you knew I wouldn't like.
I'm leaving. I can tell when I'm not welcome.
I'm taking one of these. You can't use them, you don't have thumbs!
I spent my remaining days in exile, trying to rebuild.
I finally built one wind turbine, thus saving the environment
I have saved the Nature! Feel like I've forgotten something...
23 hours until impact! How do I destroy it?
My greatest inspiration would probably tell me to build wall
And make the meteor pay for it.
But I would need so many people to start building and I have no one.
Wait... I have the bisons!
What do you mean you don't care about the meteor?!
...Because you don't have to.
I finally get the game's message.
We need to save the bison because they protect us
from giant killer asteroids.
You see
Bisons are floofy and the meteor will bounce off
their floofiness back into space.
I am completely safe..
Or we all fucking die!
Because it doesn't matter what you do. The Universe Will Whoop Your Ass.